e-bookmarking.com 2015-03-14

# Privacy Policy |

**Privacy Policy for e-bookmarking.com**

At 

e-bookmarking.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect at e-bookmarking.com and how it is used.

**Outbound Links**

e-bookmarking.com contains links to external Websites. The privacy policies of these external Websites, if any, are not covered and/or controlled by e-bookmarking.com. Technologies used on such sites may vary, so please consult their privacy policy and/or site owner to determine which technologies they utilize.

**Submissions**

e-bookmarking.com is primarily a Web Directory.  We collect information from submissions and publish this information which is viewable by our audience.  Please note that the submitters E-mail address is private and not published under any directory listing.  It is expected that any submission and/or communication in relation to listings will be viewable to the public.  This information is not sold.  
**  
Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, e-bookmarking.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes but is not limited to internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

e-bookmarking.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and Commission Junction.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to deliver the advertisements and links that appear on 

e-bookmarking.com.  They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.e-bookmarking.com has no access to or control over these cookies and web beacons which are used by third-party advertisers.  Besides collecting data such as your IP address, such technology may record the referring URL, Web Browser used, and other non-identifiable information.

DoubleClick DART Cookie .Google©, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on e-ebookmarking.com. .Googles© use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to e-ebookmarking.com and other sites on the Internet. .Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google© ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. e-bookmarkings privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Communication**

e-bookmarking.com does notify submitters by E-mail when their ads are accepted, rejected, modified, are to expire, or when listings have expired.  On occasion, we may send periodical notices to inform our submitters of valued products, services, and industry news in the form of a newsletter.

**Contact**  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at the URL below.

http://e-bookmarking.com/support/index.php

Created 23/11/2013  
Updated 02/06/2014
